[
    {
      "question": "essen",
      "correctAnswer": "yemek",
      "answer" :["icmek","denemek", "susmak"]

    },
    {
        "question": "trinken",
        "correctAnswer": "icmek",
        "answer" :["yemek","yapmak", "gelmek"]

  
      },
      {
        "question": "laufen",
        "correctAnswer": "kosmak",
        "answer" :["hoplamak","atlamak", "ziplamak"]
  
      },
      {
        "question": "gehen",
        "correctAnswer": "gitmek",
        "answer" :["gelmek","alisveris yapmak", "susmak"]
  
      },
      {
        "question": "kommen",
        "correctAnswer": "gelmek",
        "answer" :["gitmek","duymak", "koklamak"]
  
      },
      {
        "question": "kochen",
        "correctAnswer": "pisirmek",
        "answer" :["yazmak","duymak", "kizartmak"]
  
      },
      {
        "question": "lachen",
        "correctAnswer": "gülmek",
        "answer" :["aglamak","yemek", "bagirmak"]
  
      },
      {
        "question": "weinen",
        "correctAnswer": "aglamak",
        "answer" :["gülmek","sarap icmek", "icmek"]
  
      },
      {
        "question": "verhindern",
        "correctAnswer": "önlemek",
        "answer" :["sebep olmak","yatmak", "oturmak"]
  
      },
      {
        "question": "schlagen",
        "correctAnswer": "dövmek",
        "answer" :["calismak","basarmak", "bagirmak"]
  
      },
      {
        "question": "vorschlagen",
        "correctAnswer": "önermek",
        "answer" :["vurmak","bakmak", "hayal etmek"]
  
      },
      {
        "question": "schreiben",
        "correctAnswer": "yazmak",
        "answer" :["mektup","kitap", "defter"]
  
      }
  ]